hello ladies and gentlemen and welcome
你好，女士们，先生们，欢迎你
my name is Walker Skype with palo alto
我的名字是Walker Skype和palo alto
education and today but we got a treat
教育和今天，但我们得到了一个享受
for you we are gonna be recognizing
为了你我们将会认识到
faces yeah we're gonna be looking at
面对是的我们会看着
faces and we're gonna be determining
面孔，我们将决定
whether or not it's you yeah that's
不管你是 不是 那样的
right so for instance iPhone their new
因此，例如iPhone他们的新
fancy dancy gadget gizmo the iPhone X or
花哨的dancy小工具GizmoiPhone X或
whatever one it is kind of like the
不管它有什么样的
poster child of facial recognition right
面部识别权的 海报儿童
now could look at your face and tell if
现在可以看看你的脸，并告诉你是否
it's you or not so we are gonna create a
是你还是不是，所以我们要创造一个
little project that does the very same
做同样事情的小项目
thing so step one we want to go into our
所以我们想要进入我们的第一步
internet browser and hop on over to
互联网浏览器并跳转到
machine learning for kids dot code dot
机器学习为孩子点代码点
uk' other symbols and it's it's this guy
英国的其他符号就是这个人
right here
在这里
want to go to machine learning for kids
想为孩子们去机器学习
website make sure you sign in once you
网站确保您登录后
do so you're gonna go over to the
这样你就要去了
worksheets just where we are here then
工作表就在我们所在的地方
we're doing face lock face lock we're
我们正在做面锁锁我们
gonna be locking faces click that boom
将锁定面孔点击该繁荣
click that once you click that whoa
点击那个whoa后点击一下
amazing we're over here now
令人惊讶我们在这里，现在
we want to scroll down hop him hop on
我们想向下滚动跳跃他
over words to a different website which
在一个不同的网站上的文字
could perhaps look a lot like this one
也许可以期待有很多像这样的
basically we're going to go to our
基本上我们打算去我们
projects what you don't have any yet or
预测你还没有的东西或
perhaps you do but regardless we're
或许你这样做但不管我们是谁
going to make a new one that's right
打算做一个合适的新人
ladies net we're gonna make a new one
女士网我们要做一个新的
we're gonna call it face lock and yes we
我们会把它称为面锁，是的我们
get a better visual aid here so we're
在这里获得更好的视觉辅助，所以我们
gonna add a new project we're gonna name
要添加一个我们要命名的新项目
it face lock recognizing images boom
面对锁识别图像热潮
that's what we're looking for once we
这就是我们要找的，一旦我们
see this project in our list of projects
在我们的项目列表中查看此项目
we're gonna click on it and then we see
我们要点击它然后我们看到
this page what we're gonna do after this
这个页面我们将在此之后做些什么
point is we're gonna we're gonna create
重点是我们要创造
our two little boxes or we're gonna put
我们的两个小盒子或者我们要放的
our or data in which we're can collect
我们或我们可以收集的数据
in a moment but for now we're just
在片刻但是现在我们只是
creating the boxes so recall what we're
创造盒子让我们回忆起我们的想法
doing is we're trying to not just oh
我们正在努力做到的不仅仅是哦
that's a face it kind of put a box
这是一个有点放盒子的脸
around it um we're trying to determine
周围嗯，我们正在试图确定
is this you is this is this the owner of
这是你这是这个的主人
some device that we want to you know
我们想要你知道的一些设备
keep all sorts of secret and safe
保持各种秘密和安全
to Harry Potter reference if you caught
如果你抓到哈利波特参考
that Chum wearing a hair powder shirt
那个密友穿着发粉衬衫
we're wrapping it real good yes we're
我们正在包装它真的很好， 我们是
gonna add the two labels woman's gonna
要添加两个标签， 女人会
be granted and that's where we will put
被授予， 这就是我们要放的地方
your face or just some consistent face
你的脸或只是一些一致的脸
if you have had some actor or scientist
如果你有一些演员或科学家
you think is just super cool you should
你认为应该是非常酷的
get a bunch of faces of them and put it
让一群 人 脸 ，并把它
there but we'll get there in a moment
在那里，我们马上到达那里
and actually this is that moment I just
而其实这是那一刻我只是
realized so we're gonna click the webcam
意识到我们要点击网络摄像头
if you don't have a webcam if you've
如果你没有网络摄像头的话
access to some sort of cellular device
获得某种蜂窝设备
that has a camera attached to it
有一个相机连接到它
basically gets to get some photos wanna
基本上得到一些照片想要
hop on a Facebook whatever get some
跳上Facebook无论得到什么
pictures I get base and if whatever
图片我得到了基础，如果有的话
reason your face is unavailable then
因为你的脸不可用的原因
someone else's face just make sure you
别人的脸只是确保你
use the same face fun fact you don't
使用相同的面部有趣的事实，你没有
have to use a human face so you just
所以你 必须使用人脸
love your dog a little kitty cat your
爱你的狗一只小猫咪你的
fish whichever that is another option
鱼，无论哪个都是另一种选择
so whichever face you decide on just to
故取其面对你的决定 只是为了
make sure that you have at least ten of
确保你至少有十个
them any less and not only will your
他们更少，不仅是你的
machine learning not to work very well
机器学习不能很好地工作
but it actually won't work at all
但它实际上不会在所有的工作
because there's a minimum a minimum
因为至少有一个最低限度
requirement of ten so get you ten images
要求十，所以得到十个图像
and then move on to people or whatever
然后转向人或其他什么
alien thing you want that isn't you
你想要的外星人不是你
could be pictures of boxes of trees of
可能是一箱树的照片
literally anything that isn't you which
字面上任何不是你的东西
is everything else which is funny unless
是一切这是有趣的，除非
you have an identical twin don't don't
你有一个完全相同的双胞胎，不要
you cheat don't you dare alright so once
你作弊， 你不敢这么一次
we do this we're gonna go back to the
我们这样做，我们马上去回
project and we're going to the learn and
项目，我们要去学习和
test portion this is the part where the
测试部分这是其中的一部分
magic happens for the amazing machine
神奇的机器会发生魔力
learning happens over at IBM there very
学习在IBM恰好那边很
cool company who does awesome stuff like
很棒的公司谁做的很棒的东西
so many awesome stuff but that is not
这么多很棒的东西，但事实并非如此
the point of this topic now so you're
这个话题现在 所以你点
gonna click a little button as shown
要点击一个小按钮，如图所示
here and it will take some time the
在这里，它会需要一些时间
image ones typically take a little bit
图像通常需要一点点
longer so get yourself a nice cup of
更长的时间让自己好一杯
coffee over a donut or some way to pass
咖啡在甜甜圈或某种方式通过
the time and once it completes it will
时间一旦完成就会
let you know and we shall move on to the
让你知道，我们将继续前进
next section we arrive at the next step
下一节我们到达下一步
and this is where we do coding by
这就是我们编码的地方
dragging and dropping so what we do is
拖放所以我们要做的就是
we click the back to project links we're
我们点击后面的项目链接
gonna go back to that
要回到那个
this good old page we're gonna go into
这种良好的旧页我们要去进入
scratch
刮
alright so we're gonna go in here and
好吧所以我们要去这里和
actually just briefly it will be like
实际上只是简单地说就像
opening scratch
开口划伤
I forget okay if you haven't yeah are
如果你没有，我会忘记好的
you sure you're sure home so once we do
一旦我们做到了你确定你肯定回家了
that all right now I have too many too
所有现在我有太多太多
many scratches open but effectively we
许多划痕打开但有效我们
shall peruse an empty screen you don't
应仔细阅读一个空的屏幕上，你不
want an empty screen what we want is the
想要一个空屏我们想要的是什么
face lock template so you're gonna go
面锁模板，所以你要去
over to your templates your project
你的项目模板
templates and you're gonna snatch up
模板，你会抢夺
that good old fashioned face lock all
好老式 的脸全部锁定
right we now have our template but we do
我们现在有了我们的模板，但我们做到了
not have our script aka our logic where
没有我们的脚本又名我们的逻辑在哪里
things are gonna they're gonna happen
他们会发生什么事情
things are gonna be happening I don't
事情会发生我不会
know I don't have any other way to say
知道我没有任何其他办法可以说
it so we're gonna create this script
它所以我们要创建这个脚本
exactly as it is as you know they are I
就像你知道他们是我一样
guess I'm the wrong yeah boom so we have
我想我是错的， 所以我们有
these guys here just drag just drop you
这些家伙只是拖着你
got this I'm suppose we do so and this
得到这个我假设我们这样做，这
is something that I would like to impart
是我想要传达的东西
wisdom to you about when I first
我第一次见到你的智慧
attempted this I did this in the wrong
试图这样做我做错了
order I tried to go and scratch before
为了我尝试过去从头开始
I'd done anything else I'll just make it
我做了别的事情，我只会做到
right now which is another way of saying
现在这是另一种说法
when it was like hey click on the
当它像嘿点击
costumes tab I didn't have one and I got
服装选项卡我没有一个，我得到了
really frustrated because I couldn't
真的很沮丧，因为我做不到
find it but if you cope in the order
找到它，但如果你在为了 应对
that we're describing here you should
我们在这里描述你应该
have a costumes tab somewhere in there
在那里的某处有一个服装标签
so highly recommend going order because
所以强烈推荐下订单，因为
otherwise you're looking for things that
否则，你要寻找的东西，
what they they don't exist so once we do
什么他们不存在所以一旦我们这样做
so we'd like to use your webcam to take
所以我们想用网络摄像头拍摄
a picture of either your face or your
你的脸或你的脸的照片
dog's face whichever face you are trying
狗的脸无论你正在尝试什么样的脸
to detect correct all right good moving
检测到正确的好运动
on next I want to take a picture but not
接下来我想拍照但不是
none of you not your dog perhaps of some
你们没有也许有些不是你的狗
squirrel you know maybe your dog has
松鼠你知道也许你的狗有
some arch-nemesis squirrel and that is
一些拱克星松鼠，这是
the photo that you are going to detect
你要检测的照片
is not being your dog because your dog
因为你的狗不是你的狗
of course has some secret layer that is
当然有一些秘密层 是
you know locked out it locks out all
你知道锁定它会锁定所有
others who do not have your dog's face
其他没有你狗的脸
such as this this horrible evil squirrel
比如这个可怕的邪恶的松鼠
wants to come in and steal all the your
我想进来偷你所有的
dog's bones I don't know you you get it
狗的骨头我不知道你得到了它
just pick a face and take a picture so
随便挑了个鬼脸，拍照等等
now go ahead and click on the stage
现在继续前进，点击舞台
which is right there if you can't see it
如果你看不到它就在那里
we will make it even more clear this
我们会更清楚这一点
this that's this is the stage it's right
这就是这是正确的舞台
there click on that guy might looks a
点击那个家伙可能看起来像
little different don't worry about it
有点不同，不用担心
we're just at a different different
我们只是在另一个不同的地方
stage of life as we as they say you can
正如我们所说，你可以做到的生活阶段
do that and then you're gonna create the
那样做， 然后你就要创造了
following scripts these guys right here
以下脚本这些人就在这里
but when I receive these different
但是当我收到这些不同的
things
事
switch backdrop to these different
切换背景到这些不同
things such as scanning basically like
像扫描这样的东西基本上就像
I'm looking at it I'm looking at it and
我在看它，我正在看着它
then they grant it welcome welcome to
然后他们欢迎欢迎
your dog's secret hideout I'm sticking
你的狗的秘密藏身之处我坚持
yeah your dog is the secret hideout and
是的，你的狗是隐秘的秘密
it's awesome so does your cat everyone
这真棒也是如此你的猫大家
has a secret hideout even you
即使你有秘密藏身之处
I love making forts as a kid I hid
我喜欢在小时候制作堡垒
secret hideouts I hope you do too
秘密藏身处我希望你也这样做
back to the to the scratch stuff it's
它回到了划痕的东西
time to test now you're gonna click that
现在是时候测试一下你会点击那个
green flag and we're gonna see if it
绿旗，我们会看看它
works so here we are it is time ladies
在这里工作，我们是时间女士们
and gentlemen for the moment of truth we
在我们这个真理的时刻，先生们
are going to determine if fancy-pantsy
将确定是否花哨的裤子
little face lock can lock out those
小脸锁可以锁定那些
squirrels from our puppy dog hideouts
我们的小狗藏身处的松鼠
you betcha all right so we have taken
没错，别再怀疑没事 ，所以我们采取了
picture of my face this is a different
我脸上的照片与众不同
picture from the pictures that we
从照片 的画面 ，我们
trained on so this computer has never
训练有素，所以这台电脑永远不会
before seen this particular face of mine
之前看过我的这张特别的脸
so we're gonna ask it to let me in let
所以我们要让它让我进去
me in to the secret hideout and it's
我进入了秘密的藏身处，而且它是
still scanning it is still and ladies
仍在扫描它仍然和女士们
and gentlemen welcome to the hideout
先生们欢迎来到这里
boom were in alright alright sweet let's
繁荣好吧，好吧，甜蜜的
make sure though that random people this
尽管这个随机的人确定
is literally the face that comes up this
从字面上， 来了这个脸
is the first face if you type in with
是第一面，如果你在输入
ran
跑
person into Google this is the man
人到谷歌这样的男人
firmly he's the most random man which
他是最随机的人
makes it less random not the point
使它不那么随意而不是重点
this is some guy we don't know who it is
这是一些我们不知道是谁的人
but it ain't me he can't get into the
但是我不能进入他
hideout nor can he or can he or can he
藏身之处也不能，他还是可以的，他或者他可以
or can he can't no no he can't get out
或者他不能不，不，他不能出去
of here Rando dude
在这里Rando老兄
yeah it works
是的，它的工作原理
whoo so ladies and gentlemen what have
女士们，先生们，有什么
we done here today well we have
我们今天在这里做得很好
constructed an algorithm all fancy words
构造了一个算法所有花哨的单词
but we made a way for our computer to
但我们为我们的计算机做了一个方法
learn our face took a bunch of pictures
学习我们的脸上拍了一堆照片
of our face or your dog or your cat
我们的脸或你的狗或你的猫
whichever the hideout is is up to you
藏身之处取决于你
it's your part and we retrain it to
这是你的一部分，我们重新培训
recognize you and then we gave it some
认识你，然后我们给了它一些
other pictures of things and or people
事物和/或人的其他照片
or whatever that aren't you you were
或者你不是的任何人
like hey this isn't me or my dog or my
嘿，这不是我或我的狗或我的
cat whatever have you trained some
猫什么你训练了一些
machine learning things on that and we
机器学习的东西和我们
found out that it could actually do a
发现它实际上可以做到
pretty good job that you could use this
你可以用这个很好的工作
to I don't know have your phone you know
我不知道你有你的手机
like that or a secret hideout or I'm
像那个或秘密的藏身之处或我
just all about that secret hideout right
关于那个秘密藏身之处的所有权利
now yeah so pretty cool pretty pretty
现在是的，非常酷很漂亮
cool by the way this is neo from the
很酷的是这是新的
matrix they actually used a sequence
矩阵他们实际上使用了序列
sequence up a part of the movie to do
排序电影的一部分
some like crazy cool research when all
有些人喜欢疯狂的酷研究
this stuff was kind of just coming out
这东西是那种刚刚走出
you can find that on YouTube if you so
你可以在YouTube上找到它
desire it's like facial recognition
渴望就像面部识别一样
matrix which is such a good movie yeah
矩阵这是一部好电影是的
so that's a this is facial recognition
所以这就是面部识别
go to a face lock machine learning duck
去学习鸭子的脸锁机器
UK for kids and once again my name is
英国的孩子， 我的名字再一次
Walker Skype with Palo Alto education
Walker Skype与Palo Alto 教育
thank you and you have a wonderful day
谢谢你，祝你有美好的一天